Finding Aid for the Buddy Collette papers LSC.2458
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Musical Works
  - Sub-Series 2.4: Songbooks
    - Herbert Alpert and the Tijuana Brass (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Jazz America Songbook, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Rory Lewis "Just Songs" Songbook (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - West Coast Jazz Saxophone Conclave, The Book (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 2.5: Study Materials
    Exercises, practice parts, and pedagogical materials created or used by Collette.
    Arranged alphabetically by title or grouped by type.
    - Buddy Studies (Box 23, Folders 5-7)
    - Christmas Music Workshop, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Scales and Chord Patterns (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Song Forms Notes (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Study for Jean (Box 19, Folder 11, Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Work Papers for The Bridge (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 2.6: Miscellaneous Musical Materials
    Untitled, fragmentary, experimental, or unidentified musical materials, including manuscript books.
    Arranged miscellaneous titled works (A-Z), untitled works, and manuscript books; untitled materials arranged by physical size for preservation.
    - Lyrics, Various Songs (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Napkin Sketch, El Cholo Cuervo (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Song Format Pages, Duke Ellington Centennial Concerts (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Song Lists, Various Concerts and Events (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - A (Box 23, Folder 12, Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - B (Box 23, Folder 13, Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - C (Box 23, Folder 14, Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - D (Box 24, Folder 4, Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - E (Box 24, Folder 4, Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - F (Box 24, Folder 4, Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - G (Box 24, Folder 5, Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - H (Box 24, Folder 5, Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - I (Box 24, Folder 5, Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - J (Box 24, Folder 6, Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - K (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - L (Box 24, Folder 6, Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - M (Box 24, Folder 7, Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - N (Box 24, Folder 8, Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - O (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - P (Box 24, Folder 8, Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - Q (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - R (Box 24, Folder 8, Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - S (Box 26, Folders 6-7, Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - T (Box 26, Folder 8, Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Titled Works - U-Z (Box 26, Folder 9, Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Untitled Works (Box 27, Folders 3-6, Box 28, Folders 1-8, Box 29, Folders 1-6)
    - Manuscript Books (Box 29, Folder 7, Box 30, Folders 1-6)
    - Empty Instrumental Parts Folders - Leather (Box 31, Folders 1-3)
    - Empty Instrumental Parts Folders - Yamaha (Quintet labels) (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Series 3: Writings and Creative Works
  Literary and creative materials, including poetry, scripts, dramatic texts, and discography-related writings documenting Collette's creative community and interdisciplinary interests.
  Grouped by type; arranged alphabetically by title or author when possible.
  - Poetry and Jazz - Stuart Z. Perkoff, "Round About Midnite" (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Poetry and Jazz - James W. Thornton Jr., "Dry Water" (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Poetry and Jazz - James W. Thornton Jr., "Inamorata" and "Night Club" (Box 32, Folders 3)
  - Mixed Poetry (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Central Avenue - A Musical, Book by Willard Manus (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Trauma - Script, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Forward and Introduction Notes to Man of Many Parts: A Discography of Buddy Collette, compiled by Coen Hofmann (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Series 4: Printed and Ephemeral Materials
  Documents Collette's public presence through press coverage and event-related ephemera, including clippings, programs, publications, and posters.
  Arranged into four subseries by format.
  - Sub-Series 4.1: Newspaper Clippings
    Reviews and articles related to Collette's career.
    Arranged by type and alphabetically within type.
    - Reviews (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Mixed Clippings Mentioning Buddy Collette (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Mixed Clippings (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 4.2: Programs and Flyers
    Programs and flyers documenting performances, festivals, and community events.
    Arranged alphabetically by event or organization.
    - Award and Commemoration Event Programs (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Black History Celebration Flyers (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority Event Programs (Box 32, Folders 12-13)
    - Dolo Coker Tribute Flyer and Program (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Film and Theatre Performance Program (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Jazz Festival and Concert Flyers and Programs (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Jazz at Drew Legacy Music Series Program, 1991 (Box 33, Folders 3)
    - 15th Annual NAACP Theatre Awards Program, 2005 (Box 33, Folders 4)
    - Lecture Series and Research Library Event Flyers and Programs (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Miss Black America Los Angeles Program, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Participant Programs (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Scholarship Events (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Stroke Association Event Programs (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Wattstar Theatre Launch Event Program, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 4.3: Magazines and Publications
    Magazines, newsletters, books, and related publications.
    Grouped by type and arranged alphabetically.
    - Down Beat Jazz Record Reviews, Vol 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Grammy Pulse, Vol 3, No. 2, 1985 May (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Jazz Heritage Foundation, Vol. 4, No. 3 and Vol. 4, No. 5, 1983 May; 1983 September (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Jazz: Pictorial Essay by K. Abe (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jazz Times, 1996 September; 2001 April (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Los Angeles Reader, Vol. 18, No. 37, 1996 June 21 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Musica Jazz, Anno XLV, N. 8/9, 1989 August (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - National Flute Association, Inc. Newsletter, Vol 2., No. 4 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - New York Official Quick Guide, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - North Sea Jazz Festival Guide, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Performing Arts Music Center of Los Angeles County, 1997 January (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Senior Highlights, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - 43rd Annual Grammy Awards Program Book, 2001 February 21 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - The History of U.S. Navy Pre-Flight School, St. Mary's, California, Book (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Jazz Mentorship Program Annual Report, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - "Tales from the Kids #4" and "Bebop to Hiphop," David G. Brown Studios Booklets (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Verizon Presents 12th Annual Treasures of Los Angeles, 2006 April 27 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - "Sunrise on Central Avenue" Calendar, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 4.4: Posters
    Posters advertising events associated with Collette.
    Arranged chronologically when possible.
    - Jazz by the Bay Poster, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Malcolm X Union Magazine Black History Month Poster, Service Employees International Union, 1993 (Folder 35)
    - Poster of a Woman Sleeping Against a Desk (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Series 5: Photographs
  Photographic prints documenting Collette's personal life, musical career, professional relationships, and military service.
  Arranged by subject and original grouping when identifiable.
  - Buddy Collette and Friends (binder, disassembled) (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Musician's Book (binder, disassembled) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - U.S.N.R. Band, St. Mary's Pre-Flight School, Moraga, CA, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Individuals (mixed prints) (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Series 6: Audio, Audiovisual, and Digital Materials, 464 audiovisual carriers (112 open-reel audiotapes, 267 audiocassettes, 85 videocassettes); 24 born-digital carriers (21 optical discs, 3 DATs)
  Sound and moving-image recordings documenting Collette's performances, recordings, teaching, media appearances, and community activities across multiple formats.
  Arranged into three subseries by format.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO/AUDIOVISUAL/DIGITAL MATERIALS: Audio/audiovisual/digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
  - Sub-Series 6.1: 1/4" Open Reel Audiotapes
    Reel-to-reel recordings of performances, studio work, film soundtracks, interviews, and instruction.
    Arranged alphabetically by title as transcribed from original media labels and subdivided by reel size.
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Audio materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    - Sub-Sub-Series 6.1.1: 4" Diameter
      4" diameter open-reel audiotapes.
      Arranged alphabetically by title as transcribed from original media labels.
      - Reel #2, Glasspar Music, Buddy Collette, 1962 February 23 (Box 36)
      - Soundtrack Music "The Comedy of Fanny Hill," Singing Judy Cannon, Music Conducted and Played by Buddy Collette (Box 36)
    - Sub-Sub-Series 6.1.2: 5" Diameter
      5" diameter open-reel audiotapes.
      - Buddy Collette, Baby's Hungry 60" and 30", Tutti and Chris 30", Tutti and Chris "long version" (Box 36)
      - Buddy Collette Edutronic Film, 1965 (Box 36)
      - Buddy Collette #3 The City (Box 36)
      - Buddy Collette Sales Film (Box 36)
      - California City Family, Dinner, Mother's Day, 1971 (Box 36)
      - The City, Fr. Night #2 (Box 36)
      - Columbia Savings, Denver Colorado, Fin answer (Box 36)
      - Concert, Buddy Collette, 1972 January (Box 36)
      - Concert, Buddy Collette, 1972 January (Box 36)
      - Doc Young Songs (Box 36)
      - Ethiopian Trade Fair, 1966 (Box 36)
      - Fiberglass Chairs, Buddy Collette, XFER from Master (Box 36)
      - The Flemings, 1970 (Box 36)
      - Flute and Harp, Veryle Miles, Dave Shear, 1970 (Box 36)
      - Homo VI (Box 36)
      - Interview KJLH, 6pm, 1971 April 26 (Box 36)
      - Learning Corp of America (Box 36)
      - Mattel Toys Jingle, Storybook Kiddles, Background Track Tk 10, Buddy Collette (Box 36)
      - Mattel Voice Only (Box 36)
      - No Bugs Spot, Flute Alone, Buddy Collette, 1966 (Box 36)
      - Plymouth Barracuda (Box 36)
      - Plymouth Dealer Assoc, Job #862, 1966 November 28 (Box 36)
      - Practice Tape BC, 1982 (Box 36)
      - The Salesman, Buddy Collette, 1967 (Box 36)
      - San Diego Suite Part I, Mono 7 (Box 36)
      - Star Spangled Banner, Clint Murchison Jr., Dallas Cowboys, 1971 November (Box 36)
      - Sunny Side of the Street (Box 36)
      - Thurs. #2 The City (Box 36)
      - Tones at Heads (Box 36)
      - Tues Nt. Class (Box 36)
      - Tues Nt. Class (music arr. and comp motion pictures), 1972 February (Box 36)
      - 2 Songs by Bill Lewis, 1. Loves Sad, Happy...Tune, 2. Chinchilla J (Box 36)
      - [Untitled] (Box 36)
      - [Untitled] (Box 36)
      - [Untitled] (Box 36)
      - [Untitled] (Box 36)
      - [Untitled] (Box 36)
      - Veda's Shower, 1970 (Box 36)
    - Sub-Sub-Series 6.1.3: 7" Diameter
      7" diameter open-reel audiotapes.
      - Autumn Leaves, Tenor, Guitar, Chords (Box 36)
      - Barbara Perkins and Rochel (Box 36)
      - Bari and (Box 36)
      - Basic - Hampton Elgart (Box 36)
      - Brubeck (Box 36)
      - Buddy and Sorce (Box 37)
      - Buddy Collette, Al Aarons, John Collins, Joan Gionelli, Harold Jones, 1975 April 17 (Box 37)
      - Buddy Collette, Jazz Loves Paris, 1957 September 15 (Box 37)
      - Buddy Collette, Soho Party, Tape #4, 1973 November 17 (Box 37)
      - Buddy Collette [states songs], 1976 July 28 (Box 37)
      - Buddy Collette, Stein and Sieloin, 1961 December (Box 37)
      - Charles Cahill Music (Box 37)
      - Clar Solos (Box 37)
      - Club Music (Box 37)
      - Countee Cullen (Box 37)
      - Cumming Rough (Box 37)
      - Dizzy Gillespie (Box 37)
      - Duke Pearson Live, Big Band, 1975 (Box 37)
      - George Washington Carver (Box 37)
      - Gerry Mulligan, Concert Band (Box 37)
      - Hipnatize, Righteous Apple (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5212 #1 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5212 #1, 1985 October 1 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5212 #2 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5212 #5, 1985 October 1 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5212 #11 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5212 #12, 1985 October 7 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5212 #14 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5218 #4 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5218 #5 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5218 #6 (Box 37)
      - Hunter 5218 #7 (Box 37)
      - Interview with Cloie and Chico Hamilton (Box 37)
      - Japan Music (Box 37)
      - Japan Tract (Box 37)
      - "Jazz By the Bay" Part II, San Diego Concert, Buddy Collette, 1969 (Box 37)
      - Julie London, Julie At Home (Box 37)
      - Jungle Pipe and Blue Sand (Box 37)
      - lauel (Box 37)
      - Lionel Hampton (Box 37)
      - Lord Calvin Music Part III, 1971 August 8 (Box 37)
      - Million Dollar Sellers (Box 37)
      - Music and Sound, Buddy Collette, 1959 October 20 (Box 37)
      - Music and Sound, Moran (Box 38)
      - Music for Lovers Only - Jackie Gleason (Box 38)
      - Navy Film Trio, Buddy Collette, Fred Katz, Al Viola, 1966 April 29 (Box 38)
      - Polar Bear (Box 38)
      - Provocative Percussion Vol I and III (Box 38)
      - Puppets, Geo. Moran, Bank Com (Box 38)
      - Rehearsal Tape, Stella and Alto and Tenor, 1975 June (Box 38)
      - Reunion, Chico Hamilton, Buddy Collette, 1975 (Box 38)
      - Roll #8 Prod #2302 Hardcastle and McCormick, September (Box 38)
      - Side I: Around the World in 80 Days, Side II: Carnival (Box 38)
      - Side I: South Pacific, Side II: Exodus (Box 38)
      - Side I starts with Jump Up Calypso, Side II starts with South of the Border (Box 38)
      - Side I starts with Percussive Jazz, Side II starts with Making Whoopie (Box 38)
      - Singer from Donte's, Arabic (Box 38)
      - Solo Guitar, Al Viola, 1957 September (Box 38)
      - The Sound of Music (Box 38)
      - Stan Getz, Cal Jaden, Billy Higgens, Scotty La Farra, 1. Benny Golson 1 to 10, 2. Junior Mance Trio (Box 38)
      - I: Stokoski and Philadelphia Orch, 2: Nutcracker Suite, Arthur Rodzinski, N.Y. Symphony Orch (Box 38)
      - Tail "Spirit of America" Music DO NOT RUN - "Tape" (Box 38)
      - Track #1 Clar. Sounds and Alto Sound Buddy, Track #2 Rock and Roll, 1967 (Box 38)
      - Un Barque Sorl'Ocean, Pavane Tomben DC Couperin, Minuet Antique, Cales Nobles and (Box 38)
    - Sub-Sub-Series 6.1.4: 10.5" Diameter
      10.5" diameter open-reel audiotapes.
      - Buddy Collette, George Moran, Master Tape, Side I: Suite (no spreads), Side 2: Taboo, Flight, Gaugin, No One, 1959 October 13 (Box 38)
      - Buddy Collette, George Moran, Master Tape, Side 1: Taboo, Flight, Gauguin, No One, Side 2: Suite (no spreads), 1959 October 13 (Box 38)
      - Buddy Collette, James Melltom, Ve..re Jazz, 1988 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Reel 1 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Reel 2 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Reel 3 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Reel 4 (Box 39)
      - Red Callender Master Tape 2 Trk (Box 39)
      - Tape #, Latin Music with voices, Red Callender? (Box 39)
  - Sub-Series 6.2: Cassette-Based Media
    Audio and video cassette recordings from Collette's later career and educational work.
    Arranged alphabetically by title as transcribed from original media labels and subdivided by format.
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO/AUDIOVISUAL: Audio/audiovisual are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    - Sub-Sub-Series 6.2.1: Compact Audio Cassettes
      Compact audio cassette recordings documenting performances, interviews, and events.
      CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO: Audio is not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
      - Acoustic Jazz, Davis - Poshek (Box 39)
      - Ain't Nothing But A Blue Thang! Taj Mahal, Trial and Error Soundtrack (Box 39)
      - Albuquerque, 1981 February 28 (Box 39)
      - Al Viola KBCA (Box 39)
      - Bar Scene Film Project (Box 39)
      - Bass Clarinet and Piano (Box 39)
      - B.C. Interview The Jazz Players (Box 39)
      - BC Now and Then (Box 39)
      - B. Collette and Doris Argoud Interview, 1994 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette and F. Katz, L.A. Press Club, 1985 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette and L. Feather Interview (Box 39)
      - B. Collette and V. King, Interview, 1981 September (Box 39)
      - B. Collette, D. MacDonald, G. Wiggins, 1999 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette Interview w/ Bette Cox, 1983 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette Interview w/ Donna Metz, 1989 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette Jazz Camp, Santa Cruz, Monte Toyon, 1987 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette, L.A. Ensemble, Jean DeLacour, 1982 September 26 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette, 1961 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette Quintet, Centinella Park, 1977 September 4 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette Quintet, Centinella Park, 1977 September 4 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette Quintet, Donte's, 1982 (Box 39)
      - B. Collette Quintet, Kinsey Aud Museum, 1981 December 20 (Box 39)
      - Bela Bartok Concerto for Orch (Box 39)
      - Benny Carter Library of Congress, 1996 (Box 39)
      - Beth Bergman (Box 39)
      - Beyond Dreams, The Spirit of Romanticism, Dominique Piana, Harp (Box 39)
      - Bill Green and the Metronome (Box 39)
      - Black and Brown, 1972 (Box 39)
      - Bobby Rodriguez, A Latin Jazz Christmas (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette and Charles McPherson (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette and Charles McPherson, 1994 October 20 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette and Irene Kral, 1958 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette and James Newton flute track, 1988 July 4 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette and Pat Willard Interview, 1987 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette at Donte's, May, 1986 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Big Band, Watts Towers Festival, 1981 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Club, San Diego (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Concert, L.A. Press Club, 1981 May 9 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette, C. Terry, Monterey, 1977 September 17 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette, El Camino, Dolphy, 1990 May 19 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette El Camino Live #1, 1990 May 19 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Film Music (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette fl and harp, 1980 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette in Italy (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette in Italy, 1961 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette in Italy, 1961 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette It's April (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette, James Newton, Vienne France (Live), 1988 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette, Jazz Profiles, NPR (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette, KPFK, 1985 August 5 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette KXLV 88.9 fm Interview "nite journey", 1985 March (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Live at El Camino, 1990 May 19 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette "Live" at the California Plaza Spiral Court, 1989 August 5 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Live at Triforium, G. Wiggins, A. Viola, A. Jackson, J. Kirkwood, 1988 August 6 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Live Newport Concert, 1990 July 6 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette, 1956 November 19; 1957 December 16 (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Orchestra (Box 39)
      - Buddy Collette Quartet, Center Theatre, Santa Barbara, 1991 March 2 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette Quartet, Elario's, 1990 September 20 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette Quintet, Japan Theatre, 1990 September 3 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette Quintet, L.A. Festival: Japan America Theatre, 1990 September 3 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette Quintet, Newport Beach, 1990 July 6 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette Quintet, UCI Concert, 1994 May 21 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette Radio (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette Reading in Miles Davis and flute sounds, 1992 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette, S.F. #2, John Handy, Mark Isham, Brian Cooke, Jeff Nelboars, Brag Billhorn (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette with Frank Strazzeri, 1993 October 23 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette, Washington, DC, Reel 1, 1996 June 6 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette, Washington, DC, Reel 2, 1996 June 6 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Collette w/ LA Scala String Quartet, 1961 (Box 40)
      - Buddy Lessons, 1978 May-June (Box 40)
      - Buddy Teaching, 1978 (Box 40)
      - Buddy, Dunagan Piano, Lorez (Box 40)
      - Cal City and Mark Levine, 1975 (Box 40)
      - Cal City, Club Rm, B. Collette, 1974 (Box 40)
      - Cal City Jam Session, 1972 June (Box 40)
      - Cal City, 1972 (Box 40)
      - Calif. City, 1975 (Box 40)
      - Cal State Long Beach Don Para (Box 40)
      - Calvin Jackson - Gershwin (Box 40)
      - C. Basie, Knott's Berry Farm, 1980 (Box 40)
      - Centinella Park, B.C. Quintet, 1977 September 4 (Box 40)
      - Charlie Mingus #7 (Box 40)
      - Chas Mingus Early Recordings (Box 40)
      - Chico Hamilton / Buddy Collette, Queens Hotel, Las Vegas, 1992 December 14 (Box 40)
      - Collette and Mills (Box 40)
      - Collette and Mills, flute and harp album, Side #2 (Box 40)
      - Collette - Matthews, Concert, 1980 June (Box 40)
      - Concerts from the Library of Congress, Buddy Collette Big Band (Box 40)
      - Concerts from the Library of Congress, Buddy Collette Big Band (Box 40)
      - Crystal (Box 40)
      - Crystal - B. Colette, lyrics E. Shefler, copyright, 1993 (Box 40)
      - Dave Boruff - Reeds - Demo - (Box 40)
      - Dedication - Musicians' Union Bldg., 1950 January 21 (Box 40)
      - Doug Botnick (Box 40)
      - "Dr. S" (Box 40)
      - Duke Ellington #3 (Box 40)
      - Duke Ellington's Various Orchestras (Box 40)
      - Early Years I (Box 40)
      - Eddie Money, "I Died a Thousand Times", 1996 (Box 40)
      - Elaine Cohen - Les Scher Interview, Red Callendar, Radio KMUD Garder Ville, 1996 March 3 (Box 40)
      - Ella Fitzgerald Elements Interview Clips and Music (Box 40)
      - Ellington by Gillespie and BobbyEllington w/ Sinatra (Box 40)
      - Ellingtones - By David Baker (Box 40)
      - Ernestine Anderson, Azure Te, Limehouse Blues, 1959 (Box 40)
      - "Eubie" Hunting Hartford, 1979; 1980 (Box 40)
      - Excerpts from Solos (Box 40)
      - Film Music Class (Box 40)
      - Fl and Harp (Box 40)
      - Fl and Harp, 1980 (Box 40)
      - Fl and Harp, Rehearsal, Wade Marcus, 1979 (Box 40)
      - Fl and Harp Session #1, 1980 (Box 40)
      - Flute and Harp Album, Buddy Collette and Verlye Mills (Box 40)
      - Flute warm ups (Box 40)
      - For Buddy, copyright Russ Mullen, 1991 (Box 40)
      - For Mr. B - (Box 40)
      - Frank Sinatra / Duets (Box 40)
      - Frank Woodson Funeral, 1980 (Box 40)
      - French Lessonand B.C., 1991 April 12 (Box 40)
      - French Tape, BC and Jay (Box 40)
      - Gabe Pettocelli, 714-987-7385 (Box 40)
      - Garnett Brown, B. Colette (Box 40)
      - George Adams "Nightingale" (Box 40)
      - George Gershwin's Porgy and Bess (Box 40)
      - Gerry MulliganChet Baker, Chico Hamilton, Buddy Collette-Gerald Wiggins (Box 40)
      - "Good Is Love", "Remember MeIs It Love" (Box 40)
      - Gore Vidal-Day of the Deadline in the Gulf, KPFK Radio 90.7 FM (Box 40)
      - Grover Mitchell Big Band Monterey, 1978 (Box 40)
      - G. Wilson Interview, Collette, Callender, Mingus, and Woodman, 1973 December 9 (Box 40)